Office of the Provost. Administrative files of Ernest Carroll Moore. 1917-1936. UARC.0261
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Music., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Philosophy., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Physical Education for Women., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Physics., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Political Science., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Psychology., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Geology., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Academic Senate., 1926-1927. (Box 21)
- Administration, Berkeley - Comptroller's Office., 1926-1927. (Box 21)
- Departments - Training Department., 1925-1926. (Box 21)
- Education - Citya nd County Offices., 1925-1926. (Box 21)
- Education - State Offices., 1925-1926. (Box 21)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1925-1926. (Box 21)
- General Correspondence., 1925-1926. (Box 21)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events., 1925-1926. (Box 21)
- Regents., 1925-1926. (Box 21)
- Students - Fraternities and Sororities., 1925-1926. (Box 21)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1925-1926. (Box 21)
- Westwood Site., 1925-1926. (Box 21)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the University., 1926-1927. (Box 22)
- Administration, Berkeley - Association Dean of the University., 1926-1927. (Box 22)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1926-1927. (Box 22)
- Administration, Berkeley - Readers and Helpers Roll., 1926-1927. (Box 22)
- Administration, Berkeley - Recorder., 1926-1927. (Box 22)
- Administration, Berkeley - General Correspondence., 1926-1927. (Box 22)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Administrative Staff Meetings., 1926-1927. (Box 22)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Admissions., 1926-1927. (Box 22)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Advisory Administrative Board., 1926-1927. (Box 22)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Committees., 1926-1927. (Box 22)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Comptroller's OFfice, Budget Statement., 1926-1927. (Box 22)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Council of the Southern Branch., 1926-1927. (Box 22)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Examiner., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Recorder., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Secretary, Appointment., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Alumni., 1925-1926. (Box 23)
- Amendment No. 10., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Conferences., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Deans - College of Letters and Science., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Deans - Men., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Deans - Summer Session., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Deans - Teachers College., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Deans - Women., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Deapartments - Languages, French., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Department - Education., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Department - Geography., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Department - Music., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Department - Physics., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Department - Psychology., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Art., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Biological Sciences., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Economics., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - English., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Geology., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - History., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Home Economics., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Languages, Classical., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Languages, Spanish., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Library., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Library, Clark., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Music., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Philosophy., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Physical Education for Women., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Political Sciences., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Political Science, Los Angels Institute of Public Affairs., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Departments - Public Health Nursing., 1926-1927. (Box 23)
- Department - General Correspondence., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Department - Training Department., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Education - City and County Offices., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Education - State Offices., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Faculty - Responses to Moore's Letter Regarding Office and Class Schedule., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Faculty - Sabbatical Leaves, Research and Travel Grants., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Lectures, Program and Special Events - General Correspondence., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events - Dinner for Roscoe Pound., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events - Dedication of the Westwood Campus., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events - Dinner for Roscoe Pound., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Regents., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Student - Fraternities and Sororities., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Westsite Site., 1926-1927. (Box 24)
- Academic Senate., 1927-1928. (Box 25)
- Administration, Berkeley - Comptroller's Office., 1927-1928. (Box 25)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the University., 1927-1928. (Box 25)
- Administration, Berkeley - Association Dean of the University., 1927-1928. (Box 25)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1927-1928. (Box 25)
- Administration, Berkeley - Recorder., 1927-1928. (Box 25)
- Administration, UCLA - Administrative Staff Meetings., 1927-1928. (Box 25)
- Administrative, UCLA - Advisory Administrative Board., 1926-1927. (Box 25)
- General Correspondence., 1926-1927. (Box 25)
- Administration, UCLA - Committees., 1927-1928. (Box 26)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office, Budget Statements., 1927-1928. (Box 26)
- Administration, UCLA - Council., 1927-1928. (Box 26)
- Administration, UCLA - Examiner., 1927-1928. (Box 26)
- Administration, UCLA - Recorder., 1927-1928. (Box 26)
- Alumni., 1927-1928. (Box 26)
- Aquarium., 1927-1928. (Box 26)
- Building and Landscaping., 1927-1928. (Box 26)
- Deans - Men., 1927-1928. (Box 26)
- Deans - Teachers College., 1927-1928. (Box 26)
- Deans - Women., 1927-1928. (Box 26)
- Department - Annual Report of Ernest C. Moore., 1926-1927. (Box 26)
- Departments - Arts., 1927-1928. (Box 26)
- Department - English., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Department - Geography., 1926-1927. (Box 27)
- Department - Geology., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Department - Home Economics., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Department - Library., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Economics., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - General Correspondence., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - History., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Languages, Spanish., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Languages, General Correspondence., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Languages, Classical., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Library, Clark., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Music., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Philosophy., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Physical Education for Women., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Physics., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Political Science., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Psychology., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Public Health Nursing., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Departments - Training Department., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Education - City and County Offices., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Education - State Offices., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Faculty - Applications for Positions at UCLA., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Mexican Delegation., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Munthe Collection of Chinese Art., 1927-1928. (Box 27)
- Academic Senate., 1928-1929. (Box 28)
- Administation, Berkeley - General Correspondence., 1928-1929. (Box 28)
- Administration, Berkeley - Comptroller's Office., 1928-1929. (Box 28)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the College of Letter and Science., 1928-1929. (Box 28)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the University., 1928-1929. (Box 28)
- Administration, Berkeley - Association Dean of the University., 1928-1929. (Box 28)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1928-1929. (Box 28)
- Administration, Berkeley - Recorder., 1928-1929. (Box 28)
- Administration, UCLA - Administrative Staff Meetings., 1928-1929. (Box 28)
- General Correspondence., 1927-1928. (Box 28)
- Regents., 1927-1928. (Box 28)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1927-1928. (Box 28)
- Students - Praternities and Sororities., 1927-1928. (Box 28)
- Administration, UCLA - Advisory Administrative Board., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office, Budget Statements., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Administration, UCLA - Council., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Administration, UCLA - Examiner., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Administration, UCLA - Recorder., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Aquarium., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Building and Landscaping., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Conferences - University Religious Conference., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Conferences - Western Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Dean - Men., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Deans - College of Letters and Science., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Deans - Women., 1928-1929. (Box 29)
- Department - History., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Department - Library., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Art., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Biological Sciences., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Economics., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Education., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - English., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Extension., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Geography., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Geology., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Home Economics., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Languages, Classicals., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Languages, French., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Languages, Spanish., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Library, Clark., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Music., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Philosophy., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Physical Education for Women., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Physics., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Political Science., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Psychology., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Training Department., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Departments - Vocational Education Division., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Faculty - Applications for Positions at UCLA., 1928-1929. (Box 30)
- Academic Senate., 1929-1930. (Box 31)
- Administration, Berkeley - Comptroller's Office., 1929-1930. (Box 31)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the University., 1929-1930. (Box 31)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1929-1930. (Box 31)
- Administration, UCLA - Administrative Staff Meetings., 1929-1930. (Box 31)
- Administration, UCLA - Admission., 1929-1930. (Box 31)
- Faculty - Sabbatical Leaves, Research and Travel Grants., 1928-1929. (Box 31)
- General Correspondence., 1928-1929. (Box 31)
- Lecture, Programs and Special Events., 1928-1929. (Box 31)
- Organ., 1928-1929. (Box 31)
- Regents., 1928-1929. (Box 31)
- Administration, UCLA - Committees., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office, Budget Statements., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Administration, UCLA - Council., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Administration, UCLA - Recorder., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Administration, UCLA - Secretary, Appointment., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Administrative, UCLA - Advisory Administrative Board., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Alumni., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Building and Landscaping., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Conference - University Religious Conference., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Conferences - Western Addociation of Colleges and Secondary Schools., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Deans - College of Letters and Science., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Deans - Men., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Deans - Summer Session., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Deans - Teachers College., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Deans - Women., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Del Amo Foundation., 1929-1930. (Box 32)
- Department - Chemistry., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Economics., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - English., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Geography., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Geology., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - History., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Home Economics., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Language, Classical., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Languages, General Correspondence., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Library., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Mathematics., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Mechanic Arts., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Music., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Philosophy., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Physical Education for Men., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Physical Education for Women., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Physics., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Political Science., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Psychology., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Training Department., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Department - Vocational Education Division., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Departments - Art., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Departments - Biological Sciences., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Departments - Language, French., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Departments - Language, Spanish., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Departments - Library, Clark., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Departments - Vocational Education., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Education - State Offices., 1929-1930. (Box 33)
- Faculty - Applications for Position at UCLA., 1929 Jul-1930 Feb. (Box 33)
- Faculty - Application for Positions at UCLA., 1930 Mar-Jun. (Box 34)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1929-1930. (Box 34)
- Faculty - Supplementary Employment Reports., 1929-1930. (Box 34)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events., 1929-1930. (Box 34)
- Organ., 1930 Mar-Jun. (Box 34)
- Academic Senate., 1930-1931. (Box 35)
- Administration, Berkeley - Comptroller's Office., 1930-1931. (Box 35)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the University., 1930-1931. (Box 35)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1930 Jul-Oct. (Box 35)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1930 Nov-1931 Feb. (Box 35)
- General Correspondence., 1929-1930. (Box 35)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1929-1930. (Box 35)
- Administration, Berkeley - General Correspondence., 1930-1931. (Box 36)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1931 Mar-Jun. (Box 36)
- Administration, UCLA - Administrative Staff Meetings., 1930-1931. (Box 36)
- Administration, UCLA - Admission., 1930-1931. (Box 36)
- Administration, UCLA - Committees., 1930-1931. (Box 36)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office., 1930-1931. (Box 36)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office, Budget Statements., 1930-1931. (Box 36)
- Administration, UCLA - Council., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Administration, UCLA - Examiner., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Administration, UCLA - Graduate Work., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Administration, UCLA - Recorder., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Administration, UCLA - Secretary, Appointment., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Administration, UCLA - Secretary., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Alumni., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Buildings and Landscaping., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Conferences - Southern Conference Association of Colleges and University., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Conferences - Western Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Dean - Men., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Dean - Summer Session., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Deans - Colleges of Letter and Sciences., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Deans - Teachers College., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Deans - Women., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Del Amo Foundation., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Department - English., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Department - Geography., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Department - Geology., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Departments - Art., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Departments - Biological Sciences., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Departments - Economics., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Departments - Education., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Departments - Extension., 1930-1931. (Box 37)
- Department - History., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Department - Language, Spanish., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Department - Languages, French., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Department - Library., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Department - Physical Education for Women., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Department - Physics., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Department - Scripps Institution., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Home Economics., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Languages, Classical., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Music., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Philosophy., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Political Science., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Psychology., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Training Department., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Departments - Vocational Education., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Donations., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Education - City and Country Offices., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Education - State Offices., 1930-1931. (Box 38)
- Faculty - Applications for Positions at UCLA., 1930 Jul-Dec. (Box 38)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1930-1931. (Box 39)
- Faculty - Institute for Social Science Research., 1930-1931. (Box 39)
- Faculty - Sabbatical Leaves, Research and Travel Grants., 1930-1931. (Box 39)
- Lectures, Program and Special Events., 1930-1931. (Box 39)
- Academica Senate., 1931-1932. (Box 40)
- General Correspondence., 1930 Jul-1931 Mar. (Box 40)
- General Correspondence., 1931 Apr-Jun. (Box 40)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events - Dedication of Kerckhoff Hall., 1930-1931. (Box 40)
- Organ., 1930-1931. (Box 40)
- Regents., 1930-1931. (Box 40)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1930-1931. (Box 40)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1931 Jul-Nov. (Box 41)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1932 Dec-Jun. (Box 41)
- Administration, UCLA - Administrative Staff Meetings., 1931-1932. (Box 41)
- Administration, UCLA - Admissions., 1931-1932. (Box 41)
- Administration, UCLA - Committees., 1931-1932. (Box 41)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office., 1931-1932. (Box 41)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office, Budget Statements., 1931-1932. (Box 41)
- Administration, UCLA - Council., 1930-1931. (Box 42)
- Administration, UCLA - Examiner., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Administration, UCLA - Graduate Work., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Administration, UCLA - Graduate Work., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Administration, UCLA - Recorder., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Administration, UCLA - Secretary, Executive., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Administration, UCLA - Secretary, Appointment., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Alumni., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Building and Landscaping., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Conference - University Religious Conference., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Dean - Men., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Deans - College of Letters and Science., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Deans - Summer Session., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Deans - Teacher College., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Deans - Women., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Del Amo Foundation., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Department - Art., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Department - Chemistry., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Department - Extension., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Department - Geography., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Department - Geology., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Department - Home Economics., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Departments - Annual Report of Ernest C. Moore., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Departments - Astronomy., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Departments - Biological Sciences., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Departments - Economics., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Departments - English., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Departments - History., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Departments - Language, Classical., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Departments - Vocational Education Division., 1931-1932. (Box 42)
- Department - Philosophy., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Department - Physic., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Department - Physical Education for Women., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Languages, Spanish., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Languages, General Correspondence., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Languages, French., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Library., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Music., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Political Science., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Psychology., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Scripps Insitution of Oceanography., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Departments - Training Department., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Donations., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Education - City and County Offices., 1931-1932. (Box 43)
- Education - State Offices., 1931-1932. (Box 44)
- Faculty - Application for Positions at UCLA., 1932 Apr-Jul. (Box 44)
- Faculty - Applications for Positions at UCLA., 1931 Jul-1932 Mar. (Box 44)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1931-1932. (Box 44)
- Faculty - Sabbatical Leaves, Travel and Research Grants., 1931-1932. (Box 44)
- Lectures, Program and Special Events., 1931 Jul-Dec. (Box 44)
- General Correspondence., 1931 Jul-1932 Jan. (Box 45)
- General Correspondence., 1932 Feb-Jun. (Box 45)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events., 1932 Jan-Jun. (Box 45)
- Regents., 1931-1932. (Box 45)
- Students - Fraternities and Sororities., 1931-1932. (Box 45)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1931-1932. (Box 45)
- Survey of Higher Education in California., 1931-1932. (Box 45)
- Academic Senate., 1932-1933. (Box 46)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1932 Jul-Dec. (Box 46)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's OFfice., 1933 Jan-Jun. (Box 46)
- Administration, Berkeley - General Correspondence., 1932-1933. (Box 46)
- Administration, UCLA - Administrative Staff Meetings., 1932-1933. (Box 46)
- Administration, UCLA - Admissions., 1932-1933. (Box 46)
- Administration, UCLA - Committeees., 1932-1933. (Box 46)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office., 1932-1933. (Box 46)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office, Budget Statements., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Administration, UCLA - Council., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Administration, UCLA - Graduate Work., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Administration, UCLA - Recorder., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Administration, UCLA - Secretary, Appointment., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Administration, UCLA - University Associates., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Alumni., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Coliseum., 1932-1933. (Box 47)